Assalam Walekum, this is Mohammad Karar
Hussain in your watching Karar Hussain YouTube channel
list video, I have brought for you
another great part time work from home job opportunity on your demand,
here you
can earn up to ₹80000 per month, the
name of the company is ICC Lombard Hair
Insurance Agent, you
can apply for this job from any corner of India, in this
post we will talk about your eligibility, you should be
18 years or above,
minimum qualification is 10th pass, you
can apply here, you should know any one regional
language, okay you should have
basic knowledge of insurance, if
you have previous
experience of working in the insurance sector, it will be an
advantage for you here, here you have to
sell the products of ICC Lombard, here
you will get commission, share the link to apply
with description